Laura: Hello, everybody. Welcome to the class.
I’m Laura. I’m your Teacher.
OK, let’s go. Look at me.
Dan: Hi, I’m Dan. What’s your name?
Jasmine: Jasmine.
Dan: Sorry?
Jasmine: Jasmine!
Dan: Hey. What’s your phone number?
Jasmine: It’s 07700 900271.
Dan: 07700 900271.
Jasmine: Yes. Message me.
Thanks.
Ed: Hi, Dan.
Dan: Hello.
This is Jasmine. She’s in my salsa class.
Ed: Nice to meet you. My name’s Ed.
Jasmine: Nice to meet you, too.
Dan: Bye Jasmine.
Jasmine: Goodbye, Dan.
Bye, Ed.
Ed: Hi, Jasmine.
Jasmine: Ed!
Are you in the salsa class, too?
Ed: Yes, I am.
How are you?
Jasmine: I’m good, thank you.
And you?
Ed: Fine, thanks.
Laura: OK everybody, with your partners.
Ed, you’re with Jasmine.
Ed: Great! You’re my partner!
Jasmine: Yes! See you later, Dan.